<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <array name="FontFamily">
        <item>fonts/font29.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font1.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font2.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font3.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font4.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font5.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font6.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font7.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font8.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font9.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font10.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font11.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font12.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font13.TTF</item>
        <item>fonts/font14.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font15.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font16.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font17.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font18.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font19.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font20.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font21.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font22.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font23.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font24.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font25.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font26.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font27.TTF</item>
        <item>fonts/font28.TTF</item>
        <item>fonts/font30.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font31.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font32.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font33.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font34.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font35.ttf</item>
        <item>fonts/font36.ttf</item>
    </array>
    <array name="FontStyle">
        <item>Normal</item>
        <item>Bold</item>
        <item>Italic</item>
        <item>Bold Italic</item>
    </array>
    <array name="colorArray">
        <item>#4c3b3e</item>
        <item>#2b3c44</item>
        <item>#494949</item>
        <item>#f1b0db</item>
        <item>#faedf4</item>
        <item>#fcf3ec</item>
        <item>#f1b9c4</item>
        <item>#ffa621</item>
        <item>#fdc900</item>
        <item>#fffefc</item>
        <item>#fde202</item>
        <item>#ef8b00</item>
        <item>#fae452</item>
        <item>#f0331f</item>
        <item>#e58c14</item>
        <item>#7df063</item>
        <item>#31fa03</item>
        <item>#ee0c3a</item>
        <item>#f2541a</item>
        <item>#f5bdf2</item>
        <item>#d00333</item>
        <item>#231ae1</item>
        <item>#01ffff</item>
        <item>#00ff4f</item>
        <item>#fefd00</item>
        <item>#b1fefe</item>
        <item>#8affc6</item>
        <item>#fe3882</item>
        <item>#33dfeb</item>
        <item>#6feffa</item>
        <item>#fdfaff</item>
        <item>#7c1d5d</item>
        <item>#ffff07</item>
        <item>#9d9504</item>
        <item>#f5b225</item>
        <item>#ffb3ad</item>
        <item>#ffb6b7</item>
        <item>#860981</item>
    </array>
    <array name="LifeQuotess">
        <item>Stop saying I WiSH , Start saying I WILL</item>
        <item>U r Amazing U r Brave U R Strong</item>
        <item>Life is the most difficult Exam.</item>
        <item>Don’t forget to Smile</item>
        <item>Life is 10% what happens to us and 90% how we react to it.</item>
        <item>Difficult roads often lead to beautiful destination.</item>
        <item>No matter how dirty your past is ,your future is still spotless.</item>
        <item>NO EXPECTATIONS , NO DISAPPOINTMENTS.</item>
        <item>REMEMBER It s just a bad day, not a bad LIFE.</item>
        <item>Chris the past, Live for today, Dream for tomorrow.</item>
        <item>We must let go of the life we have planned, so as to accept the one that is waiting
            for us.
        </item>
        <item>There is only one happiness in this life, to love and be loved.</item>
        <item>Life is 10% what happens to you and 90% how you react to it.</item>
        <item>Do not take life too seriously. You will never get out of it alive.</item>
        <item>Do not dwell in the past, do not dream of the future, concentrate the mind on the
            present moment.
        </item>
    </array>
    <array name="InspirationQuotes">
        <item>Strive not to be a success, but rather to be of value.</item>
        <item>You miss 100% of the shots you don’t take.</item>
        <item>The best preparation for tomorrow is doing your best today.</item>
        <item>What we think, we become.</item>
        <item>Keep your face always toward the sunshine - and shadows will fall behind you.</item>
        <item>It is during our darkest moments that we must focus to see the light.</item>
        <item>“One Moment” Would you capture it or just let it slip???</item>
        <item>"Be Real" - We born to be real,not to be perfect</item>
        <item>If opportunity doesn t knock, build a door.</item>
        <item>Change your thoughts and you change your world.</item>
        <item>Your outlook is more than just what you think of the world. It is what you make of the
            world, of your life, and you have every reason to make it the best you can imagine.
        </item>
        <item>To play is to be the bridge between mastery and mystery, chaos and control, the
            foolishly brave and the bravely foolish.
        </item>
        <item>The bravest are surely those who have the clearest vision of what is before them,
            glory and danger alike, and yet notwithstanding, go out and meet it.
        </item>
        <item>We have always held to the hope, the belief, the conviction that there is a better
            life, a better world, beyond the horizon.
        </item>
        <item>Yes, I am a dreamer. For a dreamer is one who can find his way by moonlight, and see
            the dawn before the rest of the world.
        </item>
    </array>

    <array name="BirthdayQuotessss">
        <item>Let’s light the candles and celebrate this special day of your life. Happy birthday!
        </item>
        <item>You are very special and that’s why you need to float with lots of smiles on your
            lovely face. Happy birthday!
        </item>
        <item>I wish that life brings you a beautiful surprise for every candle on your bday cake!
        </item>
        <item>Let yourself do everything that you like most in life, may your Big Day be cheerful
            and happy!
        </item>
        <item>On your birthday friends wish you many things, but I will wish you only two: always
            and never. Never feel blue and always be happy!
        </item>
        <item>May you enjoy your special day to the fullest extent, buddy!</item>
        <item>My dear friend, may your special day be full of beautiful, magical and unforgettable
            moments!
        </item>
        <item>May the dream that means most to you, start coming true this year. Happy Bday!</item>
        <item>Today you are you! That is truer than true! There is no one alive who is you-er than
            you!happy bday!
        </item>
        <item>God gave us the gift of life; it is up to us to give ourselves the gift of living
            well!
        </item>
        <item>The secret to staying young is to live honestly, eat slowly, and lie about your age.
            Happy Birthday
        </item>
        <item>The birthday of my life Is come, my love is come to me.Happy Birthday</item>
        <item>A friend never defends a husband who gets his wife an electric skillet for her
            birthday.Happy Birthday
        </item>
        <item>I wanted to buy a candle holder, but the store didn t have one. So I got a cake.Happy
            Birthday
        </item>
        <item>My warmest wishes and my deepest love on your birthday and forever!</item>
    </array>
    <array name="CuteQuotes">
        <item>I am more concerned about your happiness, because I care about you more.</item>
        <item>You’re the best thing that happened to me and I mean it really.</item>
        <item>Time can never change my feelings for you.</item>
        <item>To make you smile for no reason is the only reason to make you happy.</item>
        <item>Distance and time don’t matter anymore when you are in my heart.</item>
        <item>Life is a party, but without you there is no reason to celebrate.</item>
        <item>Believe in small things that matter and that can make big differences.</item>
        <item>Never regret your choices because even bad experiences teach you a lot.</item>
        <item>Be what you want to be, not what others want to see.</item>
        <item>You’re my angel that gives me wings to fly high.</item>
        <item>Cute is when a person s personality shines through their looks. Like in the way they
            walk, every time you see them you just want to run up and hug them.
        </item>
        <item>I myself never feel that I m sexy. If people call me cute, I am happier.</item>
        <item>It s kind of fun being the cute, little one. In fact, I m finding it hard to grow out
            of that.
        </item>
        <item>Everything looks cute when it s small.</item>
        <item>She s like the rarest of jewels, too precious to be worn, and too valuable to tarnish.
        </item>
    </array>
    <array name="FriendshipQuotesss">
        <item>The greatest gift of life is friendship, and I have received it.</item>
        <item>Friendship is always a sweet responsibility, never an opportunity.</item>
        <item>A friend is what the heart needs all the time.</item>
        <item>A single rose can be my garden... a single friend, my world.</item>
        <item>One loyal friend is worth ten thousand relatives.</item>
        <item>A true friend never gets in your way unless you happen to be going down.</item>
        <item>A friend knows the song in my heart and sings it to me when my memory fails.</item>
        <item>There is nothing better than a friend, unless it is a friend with chocolate.</item>
        <item>Walking with a friend in the dark is better than walking alone in the light.</item>
        <item>Man’s best support is a very dear friend.</item>
        <item>No friendship is an accident.</item>
        <item>A good friend is like a four leaf clover; hard to find and lucky to have.</item>
        <item>I would rather walk with a friend in the dark, than alone in the light.</item>
        <item>Friendship marks a life even more deeply than love. Love risks degenerating into
            obsession, friendship is never anything but sharing.
        </item>
        <item>Sitting silently beside a friend who is hurting may be the best gift we can give.
        </item>
    </array>
    <array name="HappyQuotes">
        <item>Happy mind Happy Life.</item>
        <item>The most important thing is to enjoy your life - to be happy - it s all that
            matters.
        </item>
        <item>Be happy for this moment. This moment is your life.</item>
        <item>The purpose of our lives is to be happy.</item>
        <item>All I ask is the chance to prove that money can t make me happy.</item>
        <item>It is not how much we have, but how much we enjoy, that makes happiness.</item>
        <item>There is only one happiness in this life, to love and be loved.</item>
        <item>If you want to be happy, be.</item>
        <item>Happiness is not something ready made. It comes from your own actions.</item>
        <item>Happiness depends upon ourselves.</item>
        <item>The richer you get, the more expensive happiness becomes.</item>
        <item>I just find myself happy with the simple things. Appreciating the blessings God gave
            me.
        </item>
        <item>If people are talking behind your back, be happy that you are the one in front.</item>
        <item>I didn t find out what happiness means until I got married... and then it was too
            late.
        </item>
        <item>Everyone wants your happiness. Don t let them take it!!</item>
    </array>
    <array name="LoveQuotesss">
        <item>I look at you and see the rest of my life in front of my eyes.</item>
        <item>All, everything that I understand, I only understand because I love.</item>
        <item>I m much more me when I m with you.</item>
        <item>When love is not madness it is not love.</item>
        <item>Where there is love there is life.</item>
        <item>Let us always meet each other with smile, for the smile is the beginning of love.
        </item>
        <item>To love and be loved is to feel the sun from both sides.</item>
        <item>I feel great lucky everyday when i’m with you.</item>
        <item>Three simple words .. i love you . say it, mean it, and live by it.</item>
        <item>I fell in love with you. Not for how you look, just for who you are.</item>
        <item>You are the source of my joy, the center of my world and the whole of my heart.</item>
        <item>When I tell you I love you, I am not saying it out of habit, I am reminding you that
            you are my life.
        </item>
        <item>I don’t need paradise because I found you. I don’t need dreams because I already have
            you.
        </item>
        <item>You are the last thought in my mind before I drift off to sleep and the first thought
            when I wake up each morning.
        </item>
        <item>Everywhere I look I am reminded of your love. You are my world.</item>
    </array>
    <array name="SadQuotes">
        <item>The word  happiness  would lose its meaning if it were not balanced by sadness.</item>
        <item>We never taste a perfect joy; our happiest successes are mixed with sadness.</item>
        <item>Crying is cleansing. There s a reason for tears, happiness or sadness.</item>
        <item>Sadness is but a wall between two gardens.</item>
        <item>I smile not for that I am happy, but sometimes I smile to hide sadness.</item>
        <item>Pain is the only thing that’s telling me I’m still alive.</item>
        <item>People walk away easily but they leave their memories with us forever….</item>
        <item>Temporary happiness isn’t worth long term pain…</item>
        <item>Love is the person you think about during the sad songs…</item>
        <item>No one will ever understand how much it hurts.</item>
        <item>There’s death all around us. Everywhere we look. 1.8 people kill themselves every
            second. We just don’t pay attention. Until we do.
        </item>
        <item>As the light begins to intensify, so does my misery, and I wonder how it is possible
            to hurt so much when nothing is wrong.
        </item>
        <item>But grief makes a monster out of us sometimes . . . and sometimes you say and do
            things to the people you love that you can’t forgive yourself for.
        </item>
        <item>A lot of you cared, just not enough.</item>
        <item>Breathing is hard. When you cry so much, it makes you realize that breathing is
            hard.
        </item>
    </array>
    <array name="SmileQuotes">
        <item>A warm smile is the universal language of kindness.</item>
        <item>We shall never know all the good that a simple smile can do.</item>
        <item>A smile is happiness you ll find right under your nose.</item>
        <item>Always keep your smile. That s how I explain my long life.</item>
        <item>If the world s a veil of tears, Smile till rainbows span it.</item>
        <item>Look back, and smile on perils past.</item>
        <item>Colors are the smiles of nature.</item>
        <item>Beautiful Smile Quotes that will want you to smile all day.</item>
        <item>If you smile when no one else is around, you really mean it.</item>
        <item>I add a smile to everything I wear and that has worked great for me.</item>
        <item>Everytime you smile at someone, it is an action of love, a gift to that person, a
            beautiful thing.
        </item>
        <item>Don’t cry for a man who’s left you; the next one may fall for your smile.</item>
        <item>I love those who can smile in trouble, who can gather strength from distress, and grow
            brave by reflection.
        </item>
        <item>When someone is in a bad mood, look them in the eyes and tell them to smile. They will
            always smile and cheer up a bit.
        </item>
        <item>You make me smile like no one did before.</item>
    </array>
    <array name="SuccessQuotesss">
        <item>Do not be embarrassed by your failures, learn from them and start again.</item>
        <item>Success is simple. Do what’s right, the right way, at the right time.</item>
        <item>Action is the foundational key to all success.</item>
        <item>Success is going from failure to failure without losing enthusiasm.</item>
        <item>Things may come to those who wait, but only the things left by those who hustle.
        </item>
        <item>Life isn’t about finding yourself. Life is about creating yourself.Dats Success.
        </item>
        <item>To succeed in life, you need two things: ignorance and confidence.</item>
        <item>Judge your success by what you had to give up in order to get it.</item>
        <item>Your work is discover your world and then with all your heart give yourself to
            it.success yours.
        </item>
        <item>Success usually comes to those who are too busy to be looking for it.</item>
        <item>Keep your face always toward the sunshine and shadows will fall behind you.</item>
        <item>Let us make our future now, and let us make our dreams tomorrow’s reality.</item>
        <item>All you need is the plan, the road map, and the courage to press on to your
            destination.
        </item>
        <item>Try to be a rainbow in someone’s cloud.</item>
        <item>Light tomorrow with today.</item>
    </array>


    <array name="AnniversaryQuotes">
        <item>
             Happy Anniversary to my dear love and very best friend.
        </item>
        <item>
            True love is spending one day getting married and the rest of your life feeling glad you
            did. Happy Anniversary.
        </item>
        <item>
            Happy anniversary. Sweet heart, I love you more than word can say.
        </item>
        <item>
            You both are a wonderful example of love, relation and family. Happy anniversary.
        </item>
        <item>
            May you live as long as you wish and love as long as you live.
        </item>
        <item>
            There is no more lovely, friendly and charming relationship, communion or company than a
            good marriage.
        </item>
        <item>
            A lot of good love can happen in ten years, Happy Anniversary..
        </item>
        <item>
            That there s no more important decision in life than who you marry.happy Anniversary.
        </item>
        <item>
            Marriage is the most natural state of man, and... the state in which you will find solid
            happiness.
        </item>
        <item>
            In the Waltz of Life, you have proved to be the perfect dancing partners for each other
            and forever. Happy anniversary.
        </item>
        <item>
            The fact that you dont behave like a typical husband-wife makes your marriage perfect.
            Happy anniversary.
        </item>
        <item>
            A real relationship is when destinies align, souls connect and hearts beat for each
            other, forever and ever just like yours.Happy anniversary.
        </item>
        <item>
            Relationships are not about give and take, they re about share and care. Happy
            anniversary.
        </item>
        <item>
            The echo of your love and the sound of the sea have a few things in common they are both
            constant, soulful and eternal. Happy anniversary.
        </item>
        <item>
            Real relationships are when you dont have to pretend to be someone else, just to be
            liked for being someone you re not. Happy anniversary.
        </item>
        <item>
            True love is spending one day getting married. and the rest of your life feeling glad
            you did. Happy Anniversary.
        </item>
        <item>
            If I had my life to live over again next time I would find you sooner so that I could
            love you longer. Happy Anniversary to us.
        </item>
        <item>
            Since I wrote to you last we have got our chapel beautifully lighted with gas and have
            had our anniversary.
        </item>
        <item>
            I wish there was a word more than love itself to convey what I feel for you, happy
            anniversary.
        </item>
        <item>
            Real love stories never have endings, happy anniversary.
        </item>
    </array>


    <array name="AtittudeQuotes">
        <item>
            An attitude is an inward thought that wiggles its way out.
        </item>
        <item>
            I am not cranky. I just have a violent reaction to stupid people.
        </item>
        <item>
            There can be no positive result through negative attitude. Think positive. Live
            positive.
        </item>
        <item>
            People may hear your words, but they feel your attitude.
        </item>
        <item>
            For success, attitude is equally as important as ability.
        </item>
        <item>
            Weakness of attitude becomes weakness of character.
        </item>
        <item>
            I m not changed it s just I grew up and you should try too.
        </item>
        <item>
            I never insult people I only tell them what they are.
        </item>
        <item>
            My attitude based on how you treat me.
        </item>
        <item>
            I am poor. I can t pay attention in class room.
        </item>
        <item>
            Excuse me. I found something under my shoes oh its your Attitude.
        </item>
        <item>
            Please dont get confused between my personality and my attitude.
        </item>
        <item>
            My personality is who I am and my attitude depends on who you are!
        </item>
        <item>Im Not Special , Im Just Limited Edition.</item>
        <item>
            Life will give you exactly what you need, not what you want.
        </item>
        <item>
            I dont have an attitude, I have standards for the people who are supposed to be my
            friends.
        </item>
        <item>
            Our attitude towards others determines their attitude towards us.
        </item>
        <item>
            Cock your hat - angles are attitudes.
        </item>
        <item>
            You know what s funny to me? Attitude.
        </item>
        <item>
            When you are thwarted, it is your own attitude that is out of order.
        </item>
    </array>


    <array name="BirthdayQuotes">
        <item>
            Today you are you! That is truer than true! There is no one alive who is you er than
            you.
        </item>
        <item>
            God gave us the gift of life; it is up to us to give ourselves the gift of living well.
        </item>
        <item>
            Don t just count your years, make your years count, happy birthday..
        </item>
        <item>
            The way I see it, you should live everyday like its your birthday.
        </item>
        <item>
            Our birthdays are feathers in the broad wing of time.
        </item>
        <item>My life is better with every year of living it.</item>
        <item>
            Every year on your birthday, you get a chance to start new.
        </item>
        <item>Let them eat cake, happy birthday....</item>
        <item>
            Today is a perfect day to tell that you are nothing less than one of my family member! I
            Wish you a very warm and happy birthday.
        </item>
        <item>
            happy b day bro Thanks for being my brother. I look so much better in all those family
            photos with you there.
        </item>
        <item>
            Happy Birthday, to my sweet brother. May God bless you with all his warmth and care. May
            your birthday bring loads of joy and fun to your world
        </item>
        <item>
            You are the best sister that I have ever had. Even in my imagination. Happy Birthday to
            my lovely sis.
        </item>
        <item>
            Happy Birthday, dear husband. May you always fly high in life and touch all your dreams.
            With lots of love, your wife.
        </item>
        <item>
            This is just to let you know that you are the one I was waiting for! Happy Birthday My
            Love.
        </item>
        <item>
            Happy birthday to the love of my life (my lovely wife). I can t wait to celebrate
            tonight when we blow out the candles and turn out the lights.
        </item>
        <item>
            My dear wife I fall in love again every time that I see you. Hope you are happy with me.
            Happy Birthday.
        </item>
        <item>
            Kids are supposed to make their parents proud but I am proud to tell people that you are
            my Mom. Happy Birthday Mom.
        </item>
        <item>
            Your soul is pure, your heart is priceless, and your wisdom is astounding. Happy
            birthday, Dad.
        </item>
        <item>
            Happy birthday to my best friend the one who laughs at my jokes and cries with me during
            my heartaches. I will always be here for you.
        </item>
        <item>
            You have been there for me no matter what. I am so excited to share your special day
            with you. Your birthday is going to be truly special.
        </item>
    </array>


    <array name="DreamsQuotes">
        <item>
            A dream doesn t become reality through magic; it takes sweat, determination and hard
            work.
        </item>
        <item>
            All our dreams can come true, if we have the courage to pursue them.
        </item>
        <item>
            You have to dream before your dreams can come true.
        </item>
        <item>
            Hold fast to dreams, for if dreams die, life is a broken-winged bird that cannot fly.
        </item>
        <item>
            Reality is wrong. Dreams are for real.
        </item>
        <item>
            I dream of painting and then I paint my dream.
        </item>
        <item>
            Nothing happens unless first we dream.
        </item>
        <item>
            Dreaming of a tomorrow, which tomorrow, will be as distant then as this today.
        </item>
        <item>
            Man is a genius when he is dreaming.
        </item>
        <item>
            A daydream is an evasion.
        </item>
        <item>
            Dreams must be heeded and accepted. For a great many of them come true.
        </item>
        <item>
            Our dreams drench us in sense, and sense steeps us again in dreams.
        </item>
        <item>
            Dream and give yourself permission to envision a You that you choose to be.
        </item>
        <item>
            Each man should frame life so that at some future hour fact and his dreaming meet.
        </item>
        <item>
            One of the most adventurous things left us is to go to bed. For no one can lay a hand on
            our dreams.
        </item>
        <item>
            The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams.
        </item>
        <item>
            Dreams are the touchstones of our characters.
        </item>
        <item>
            Dreams have but one owner at a time. That is why dreamers are lonely.
        </item>
        <item>
            Hold fast to dreams For when dreams go Life is a barren field Frozen with snow.
        </item>
        <item>
            Everybody s a dreamer.
        </item>
        <item>
            We are the makers of dreams, the dreamers of dreams.
        </item>
    </array>

    <array name="EducationQuotes">
        <item>
            Education is the most powerful weapon which you can use to change the world.
        </item>
        <item>
            Education is not preparation for life; education is life itself.
        </item>
        <item>
            Education is the key to unlock the golden door of freedom.
        </item>
        <item>
            Education is the movement from darkness to light.
        </item>
        <item>
            An investment in knowledge pays the best interest.
        </item>
        <item>
            Develop a passion for learning. If you do, you will never cease to grow.
        </item>
        <item>
            The goal of education is the advancement of knowledge and the dissemination of truth.
        </item>
        <item>
            The world is a book and those who do not travel read only one page.
        </item>
        <item>
            The past has no power over the present moment.
        </item>
        <item>
            Intelligence plus character-that is the goal of true education.
        </item>
        <item>
            Marriage can wait, education cannot.
        </item>
        <item>
            Education is the kindling of a flame, not the filling of a vessel.
        </item>
        <item>
            Self-education is, I firmly believe, the only kind of education there is.
        </item>
        <item>
            To me education is a leading out of what is already there in the pupil s soul.
        </item>
        <item>
            In learning you will teach, and in teaching you will learn.
        </item>
        <item>
            Education is not the filling of a pail, but the lighting of a fire.
        </item>
        <item>
            Formal education will make you a living; self-education will make you a fortune.
        </item>
        <item>
            The only thing that interferes with my learning is my education.
        </item>
        <item>
            Books, the children of the brain.
        </item>
        <item>
            Education is a progressive discovery of our own ignorance.
        </item>
    </array>

    <array name="FriendshipQuotes">
        <item>
            Friendship marks a life even more deeply than love.
        </item>
        <item>
            The great thing about new friends is that they bring new energy to your soul.
        </item>
        <item>
            A sweet friendship refreshes the soul.
        </item>
        <item>
            There s not a word yet, for old friends who ve just met.
        </item>
        <item>
            When a woman becomes her own best friend, life is easier.
        </item>
        <item>
            A real friend is one who walks in when the rest of the world walks out.
        </item>
        <item>
            True friendship comes when the silence between two people is comfortable.
        </item>
        <item>
            A single rose can be my garden a single friend, my world.
        </item>
        <item>
            One s friends are that part of the human race with which one can be human.
        </item>
        <item>
            No person is your friend who demands your silence, or denies your right to grow.
        </item>
        <item>
            If you make friends with yourself you will never be alone.
        </item>
        <item>
            It is not so much our friends help that helps us, as the confidence of their help.
        </item>
        <item>
            To the world you may be just one person, but to one person you may be the world.
        </item>
        <item>
            True friends are like diamonds bright, beautiful, valuable, and always in style.
        </item>
        <item>
            A true friend is someone who sees the pain in your eyes while everyone else believes
            your smile.
        </item>
        <item>
            Friends are people who know you really well and like you anyway.
        </item>
        <item>
            A true friend, sees the first tear, catches the second and stops the third.
        </item>
        <item>
            Sometimes my best friend understands me, better than I understand myself.
        </item>
        <item>
            Being Honest may not get you lot of friends but still always get you the right ones.
        </item>
        <item>
            To my friends : Thanks for being there for me. I m grateful for you all.
        </item>
    </array>


    <array name="GeniusQuotes">
        <item>
            I am not random, you just can’t think as fast as me.
        </item>
        <item>
            Use your eyes to see the possibilities not the problems.
        </item>
        <item>
            Genius is only a superior power of seeing.
        </item>
        <item>
            Genius always finds itself a century too early.
        </item>
        <item>
            The difference between stupidity and genius is that genius has its limits.
        </item>
        <item>
            If you can’t explain it simply, you don’t understand it well enough.
        </item>
        <item>
            Trust me. I’m a GENIUS.
        </item>
        <item>
            Man is a genius when he is dreaming.
        </item>
        <item>
            Genius is eternal patience.
        </item>
        <item>
            Genius is 1% inspiration and 99% perspiration.
        </item>
        <item>
            The distance between insanity and genius is measured only by success.
        </item>
        <item>
            Don’t be the same, be better.
        </item>
        <item>
            There was never a genius without tincture of madness.
        </item>
        <item>
            genius is talent set on fire by courage.
        </item>
        <item>
            I am a misunderstood genius. "What’s misunderstood"? Nobody thinks I’m a genius.
        </item>
    </array>

    <array name="LifeQuotes">
        <item>
            Life is really simple, but we insist on making it complicated.
        </item>
        <item>
            Life isn t about finding yourself. Life is about creating yourself.
        </item>
        <item>
            We do not remember days, we remember moments.
        </item>
        <item>
            Life is not a problem to be solved, but a reality to be experienced.
        </item>
        <item>
            Life s most persistent and urgent question is,  What are you doing for others ?
        </item>
        <item>
            The good life is one inspired by love and guided by knowledge.
        </item>
        <item>
            One way to get the most out of life is to look upon it as an adventure.
        </item>
        <item>
            Life is a tragedy when seen in close-up, but a comedy in long-shot.
        </item>
        <item>
            You only live once, but if you do it right, once is enough.
        </item>
        <item>
            To live is the rarest thing in the world. Most people exist, that is all.
        </item>
        <item>
            Good friends, good books, and a sleepy conscience: this is the ideal life.
        </item>
        <item>
            Sometimes the questions are complicated and the answers are simple.
        </item>
        <item>
            If you dont know where you re going, any road ll take you there.
        </item>
        <item>
            This life is hard, but it is harder if you are stupid.
        </item>
        <item>
            Death ends a life, not a relationship.
        </item>
        <item>
            Where there is love there is life.
        </item>
        <item>
            All the world is made of faith, and trust, and pixie dust.
        </item>
        <item>
            May you live every day of your life.
        </item>
        <item>
            Open your eyes, look within. Are you satisfied with the life you re living?
        </item>
        <item>
            With renunciation life begins.
        </item>
    </array>

    <array name="LoveQuotes">
    <item>
        God is keeping me alive but you are keeping me in love.
    </item>

    <item>
        I dont need paradise because I found you.
        I dont need dreams because I already have you.
    </item>

    <item>
        Everywhere I look I am reminded of your love. You are my world.
    </item>
    <item>
        If I know what love is, it is because of you.
    </item>
    <item>
        I can t stop thinking about you, today  tomorrow always.
    </item>
    <item>
        When I look into your eyes I see the mirror of my soul.
    </item>
    <item>
        I love you every step of the way.
    </item>
    <item>
        Together with you is my favorite place to be.
    </item>
    <item>
        I still fall in love with you every day!
    </item>
    <item>
        Your beauty leaves me speechless.
    </item>
    <item>
        And when I open my eyes in the morning, I thirst for your touch.
    </item>
    <item>
        My heart is perfect because you are in it.
    </item>
    <item>
        My heart made it s choice, and it chose you.
    </item>
    <item>
        When it comes to love do not ever settle for anything less than magical.
    </item>
    <item>
        I write because it is the only way i can reach you.
    </item>
    <item>
        There is no cosmetic to gain a beauty like yours.
    </item>
    <item>
        I am here, I will always be here. Watching you, loving you.
    </item>
    <item>
        When it comes to love, Princess, rules blur, and traditions fade.
    </item>
    <item>
        Being present to yourself in love and with kindness is the ultimate gift.
    </item>
    <item>
        Every moment spent with you is like a beautiful dream come true. I love you.
    </item>
    </array>


        <array name="ManQuotes">
        <item>
            The real man smiles in trouble, gathers strength from distress, and grows brave by reflection.
        </item>
        <item>
            I live, like every real man, in my work.
        </item>
        <item>
            Nothing great will ever be achieved without great men, and men are great only if they are determined to be so.
        </item>
        <item>
            Men are born to succeed, not to fail.
        </item>
        <item>
            Honor is simply the morality of superior men.
        </item>
        <item>
            A woman simply is, but a man must become.
        </item>
        <item>
            Men, even when alone, lighten their labors by song, however rude it may be.
        </item>
        <item>
            A real man won’t date the most beautiful girl in the world - He’ll date the girl that makes his world beautiful.
        </item>
        <item>
            A great man isn’t afraid to do what is right , no matter what.
        </item>
        <item>
            The mark of real man , is a man who can allow himself to fall deeply in love with a woman.
        </item>
        <item>
            Wise man speaks only of what they know.
        </item>
        <item>
            Try not become a man of success, Rather become a man of value.
        </item>
        <item>
            Man needs his difficulties because they are necessary to enjoy success.
        </item>
        <item>
            No man is rich enough to buy his past.
        </item>
        <item>
            Remember , no man is a failure , who has friends.
        </item>
        </array>

    <array name="MissuQuotes">
    <item>
        I only miss you when I m breathing.
    </item>
    <item>
        If I could plant a flower for every time I miss you, I could walk through my garden forever.
    </item>
    <item>
        My eyes await your return. Please come back soon. I miss you.
    </item>
    <item>
        Sometimes a simple I miss you changes everything.
    </item>
    <item>
        I miss you when something really good happens, because you are the one I want to share it with.
    </item>
    <item>
        I think I ll miss you forever like the stars miss the sun in the morning skies.
    </item>
    <item>
        You may be out of my sight but never out of my mind. I Miss You.
    </item>
    <item>
        If I had a single flower for every time I think about you, I could walk forever in my garden.
    </item>
    <item>
        If ever I see you smile and know that it is not for me, that is when I will miss you the most.
    </item>
    <item>
        I pretend to ignore you, but I really just miss you.
    </item>
    <item>
        Time goes by a lot slower when you miss the one you love.
    </item>
    <item>
        Miss you in all paths of my life.
    </item>
    <item>
        I did three things today; miss you, miss you, and miss you.
    </item>
    <item>
        I dropped a tear in the ocean. The day you find it is the day I will stop missing you.
    </item>
    <item>
        You may be out of sight but never out of mind, i miss you.
    </item>
    <item>
        If you think missing me is hard, you should try missing you.
    </item>
    <item>
        A day without you is like a day without sunshine I miss you.
    </item>
    <item>
        I miss your love I miss your touch, But I m feeling you everyday.
    </item>
    <item>
        I m a fish out of water without you....I miss you.
    </item>
    <item>
        Is your heart still mine? I wanna cry sometimes. I miss you.
    </item>
    </array>

    <array name="MoneyQuotes">
    <item>
        A little thought and a little kindness are often worth more than a great deal of money.
    </item>
    <item>
        A wise man should have money in his head, but not in his heart.
    </item>
    <item>
        The lack of money is the root of all evil.
    </item>
    <item>
        All I ask is the chance to prove that money can t make me happy.
    </item>
    <item>
        A billion here, a billion there, and pretty soon you re talking about real money.
    </item>
    <item>
        If I have enough money to eat I m good.
    </item>
    <item>
        Where large sums of money are concerned, it is advisable to trust nobody.
    </item>
    <item>
        If you can count your money, you dont have a billion dollars.
    </item>
    <item>
        I am happy to make money. I want to make more money, make more music.
    </item>
    <item>
        Money is only a tool. It will take you wherever you wish, but it will not replace you as the driver.
    </item>
    <item>
        I dont think business news is just for old white men with money.
    </item>
    <item>
        A wise person should have money in their head, but not in their heart.
    </item>
    <item>
        Money is a terrible master but an excellent servant.
    </item>
    <item>
        The real measure of your wealth is how much you would be worth if you lost all your money.
    </item>
    <item>
        Money is a terrible master but an excellent servant.
    </item>
    <item>
        Wealth is the ability to fully experience life.
    </item>
    <item>
        Never spend your money before you have it.
    </item>
    <item>
        The best thing money can buy is financial freedom.
    </item>
    <item>
        Money is usually attracted, not pursued.
    </item>
    <item>
        If you would be wealthy, think of saving as well as getting.
    </item>
    </array>

        <array name="SayingsQuotes">
        <item>
            Have  the courage to follow your heart and intuition . They somehow know what you truly want to become.- Steve Jobs
        </item>
        <item>
            I destroy my enemy when I make him my friend. - Abraham Lincoln
        </item>
        <item>
            First They ignore you , then they laugh at you , then they fight with you , then you win. - Mahatma Gandhi
        </item>
        <item>
            Education is the most powerful weapon which you can use to change the world. - Nelson Mandela
        </item>
        <item>
            Knowing is not enough , we must apply. Willing is not enough , we must do. - Bruce Lee
        </item>
        <item>
            Throughout life people will make you mad , disrespect you and treat you bad . Let God deal with the things they do , cause hate in your heart will consume you too.. - Will Smith
        </item>
        <item>
            An eye for an eye only ends up making the whole world blind. -  Mahatma Gandhi
        </item>
        <item>
            Everything should be made as simple as possible , but not simpler.- Albert Einstein
        </item>
        <item>
            Be less curious about people and more curious about ideas. - Marie Curie
        </item>
        <item>
            If you born poor it’s not your mistake . But if you die poor it s your mistake. - Bill Gates
        </item>
        <item>
            If you judge people then you have no time to love them. - Mother Teresa
        </item>
        <item>
            People may hear your words, but they feel your attitude. - John C.Maxwell
        </item>
        <item>
            I have many problems in my life but my lips don’t know that. They always smiles. - Charlie Chaplin
        </item>
        <item>
            If you want to live a happy life , tie it to a goal. Not to people or things. - Albert Einstein
        </item>
        <item>
            I didn’t fail the test , I just found 100 ways to do it wrong. - Benjamin Franklin
        </item>
        <item>
            Many of life’s failures are people who did not realize how close they were to success when they gave up. - Thomas Edison
        </item>
        <item>
            Remember that the happiest people are not those getting more but those giving more.-H.Jackson Brown Jr.
        </item>
        <item>
            Creativity comes from a conflict of ideas. - Donatello Versace
        </item>
        <item>
            Well done is better that well said . -  Benjamin Franklin
        </item>
        <item>
            Success is a lousy teacher. It seduces smart people into thinking they can’t lose. - Bill Gates
        </item>
        </array>

        <array name="SuccessQuotes">
        <item>
            The starting point of all achievement is desire.
        </item>
        <item>
            Success is simple. Do what s right, the right way, at the right time.
        </item>
        <item>
            Success is not final, failure is not fatal: it is the courage to continue that counts.
        </item>
        <item>
            Success is not the key to happiness. Happiness is the key to success.
        </item>
        <item>
            Action is the foundational key to all success.
        </item>
        <item>
            If you love what you are doing, you will be successful.
        </item>
        <item>
            However difficult life may seem, there is always something you can do and succeed at.
        </item>
        <item>
            Success is nothing more than a few simple disciplines, practiced every day.
        </item>
        <item>
            Success is how high you bounce when you hit bottom.
        </item>
        <item>
            All you need in this life is ignorance and confidence, and then success is sure.
        </item>
        <item>
            The successful man will profit from his mistakes and try again in a different way.
        </item>
        <item>
            Success is achieved and maintained by those who try and keep trying.
        </item>
        <item>
            For success, attitude is equally as important as ability.
        </item>
        <item>
            Before anything else, preparation is the key to success.
        </item>
        <item>
            Success is focusing the full power of all you are on what you have a burning desire to achieve.
        </item>
        <item>
            Success is the sum of small efforts, repeated day-in and day-out.
        </item>
        <item>
            Strive not to be a success, but rather to be of value.
        </item>
        <item>
            The secret of my success is a two word answer: Know people.
        </item>
        <item>
            Eighty percent of success is showing up.
        </item>
        <item>
            Success is counted sweetest by those who never succeed.
        </item>
        <item>
            The ladder of success is best climbed by stepping on the rungs of opportunity.
        </item>
        </array>

    <array name="WisdomQuotes">
    <item>
        Knowledge speaks but Wisdom listens.
    </item>
    <item>
        Be wise enough to walk away from the nonsense around you.
    </item>
    <item>
        Wisdom is a supreme part of happiness.
    </item>
    <item>
        We can’t solve our problems with the same level of thinking that created  them.
    </item>
    <item>
        Don’t let anyone ever dull your sparkle.
    </item>
    <item>
        Patience is the companion of wisdom.
    </item>
    <item>
        When someone has offended me , I try to raise my soul so high that the offense cannot reach it.
    </item>
    <item>
        Knowledge minus Ego equals Wisdom.
    </item>
    <item>
        Wisdom is the reward of experience and should be shared.
    </item>
    <item>
        Happiness depends upon ourselves.
    </item>
    <item>
        Never give someone the opportunity to waste your time twice.
    </item>
    <item>
        Wisdom is the ability to learn from change.
    </item>
    <item>
        Wisdom comes from experience . Experience is often a result of lack of wisdom.
    </item>
    <item>
        Silence is the sleep that nourishes wisdom.
    </item>
    <item>
        Crying is not a sign of weakness. It’s a sign of having tried too hard to be strong for too long.
    </item>
    <item>
        Knowing yourself is the beginning of all wisdom.
    </item>
    <item>
        Be the change you wish to see in the world…
    </item>
    <item>
        Knowledge is knowing a tomato is a fruit . Wisdom is not putting it into a fruit salad.
    </item>
    <item>
        Efforts and courage are not enough without purpose and direction.
    </item>
    <item>
        Stop hating yourself for everything you are not. Start loving yourself for everything that you are.
    </item>
    </array>
    <array name="WomanQuotes">
    <item>
        A WOMAN brought you into this world , so you have no rights to disrespect one.
    </item>
    <item>
        Don t be a woman that needs a man ... Be a woman a man needs!
    </item>
    <item>
        I am not a princess, i m a queen. I can handle things on my own.
    </item>
    <item>
        I am not like most girls that s where you made your first mistake.
    </item>
    <item>
        Every woman is Beautiful, It just takes the right man to see it.
    </item>
    <item>
        I ll never be the girl you want me to be.. Because I am a woman I need to be..
    </item>
    <item>
        Confidence is ornament.. Wear it daily.</item>
    <item>
        I dont need a relationship to define who I am. I ll be fine..I am a strong woman.
    </item>
    <item>
        Women are made to be loved, not to be  Understood.
    </item>
    <item>
        True beauty in a woman is reflected in her soul.
    </item>
    <item>
        Always be a first-rate version of yourself, Instead of a second-rate version of somebody else.
    </item>
    <item>
        Classy woman never lose their DIGNITY.
    </item>
    <item>
        For most of history , Anonymous was a woman.
    </item>
    <item>
        A charming woman doesn t follow the crowd. She is herself.
    </item>
    <item>
        Happy girls are the Prettiest.
    </item>
    <item>
        Sweet as Sugar. Hard as Ice. Hurt me once , I ll kill you Twice.
    </item>
    <item>
        There is no force equal to a woman determined to rise.
    </item>
    <item>
        Act like a LADY , Think like a BOSS.
    </item>
    <item>
        Be like a diamond , precious and rare , not like a stone found everywhere...
    </item>
    <item>
        A girl should be like a butterfly . Pretty to see , hard to catch.
    </item>
    </array>
</resources>
